<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bangladesh Eye Hospital</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">drawer_open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">drawer_close</string>
    <string name="version_unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="app_version">Version</string>
    <string name="logo_description">Logo Description</string>

    <string name="long_lorem_ipsum_2">
   Since its humble beginning over 9 years ago, Bangladesh Eye Hospital Ltd. has come a long way. Today, Bangladesh Eye Hospital Ltd. is synonymous with world-class eye care and expertise. We pride ourselves in being the #1 eye hospital in Bangladesh.

\n\nBangladesh Eye Hospital Ltd. has now become the trendsetter for the eye care sector in the country. Our aim is to serve the community with outstanding patient care and the latest in medical advancements. We have always felt a responsibility to offer healthcare consumers the latest in advanced eye care at an affordable cost with a focus on superior customer service.

\n\nToday, our family is growing bigger and bigger. At present Bangladesh Eye Hospital Ltd. have 32 consultants, 34 medical officers and over 250 staff. Each trained to give exemplary care to every patient, without discrimination.
    </string>

    <string name="long_lorem_ipsum">
       I attribute the credit for the overwhelming success of Bangladesh Eye Hospital Ltd. to my team. For they have always shared responsibilities equally, celebrated every achievement and extended a firm helping hand at the time of crisis. It is with their support, courage and motivation that I have been able to tread this memorable path.

\n\nTogether, with your support, I am certain that we can grow even bigger and go on to become the best eye care service provider in the region.
    </string>



    <string name="long_lorem_ipsum_3">
  Vision is a gift from God to all of us. To lead a normal life, good eye sight is essential to each and every human being. Now-a-days advanced eye care hospitals not only provide good treatment, but also offer awareness on preventable eye diseases. With this vision in mind Bangladesh Eye Hospital &amp; Institute Ltd. was built to provide world-class eye care to the people of Bangladesh.

\n\nOur slogan “Eye Care, We Care” upholds our purpose to provide treatment for people from all walks of life. Our state of the art technical equipments, experienced consultants and skilled eye care personnel deliver the best  service to all our patients.

\n\nWe constantly strive to excel in our eye treatment and we are committed to serve every individual who walks through the doors of Bangladesh Eye Hospital &amp; Institute Ltd. We hold our core values of integrity, quality care, commitment and undeterred professionalism very close to our heart.
    </string>

    <string name="long_lorem_ipsum_78">
       We enhance our patients’ health care through continuously upgrading our knowledge and skills of implementation in updated management systems. Thus, quality and a vast space for improvement remain a constant commitment in Bangladesh Eye Hospital &amp; Institute Ltd.

\n\nWe invite you with open arms to become better acquainted with our pride - Bangladesh Eye Hospital &amp; Institute Ltd.
    </string>
</resources>
